Guide to The Alfred C. Berol Collection of Lewis Carroll 1845 - 1993 MSS 057
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 1: Correspondence
  - Subseries 1A: Correspondence from Charles L. Dodgson
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, October 22, 1886 (371) 5.5 x 6.75., 0923 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, October 26, 1886 (372) 5.5 x 6.75., 0926 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, October 28, 1886 (373) 5.5 x 6.75., 0931 (Box 3, Folder 217)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, October 29, 1886 (374) 5.5 x 6.75., 0935 (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 8pp. The Chestnuts, Guildford, October 31, 1886 (375) 7 x 4.5 (Cohen pg. #: 643)., 0938 (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, November 2, 1886 (376) 7 x 9., 0940 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 5, 1886 (377) 7 x 9., 0944 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 6, 1886 (378) 5.5 x 6.75., 0948 (Box 3, Folder 222)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 7, 1886 (379) 5.5 x 6.75., 0951 (Box 3, Folder 223)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 8, 1886 (380) 5.5 x 6.75., 0955 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 12, 1886 (381) 5.5 x 6.75., 0960 (Box 3, Folder 225)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 28, 1886 (352) Cyclostyle. 8 x 4.5., 0961 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 29, 1886 (382) 6 x 7.5., 0964 (Box 3, Folder 227)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 30, 1886 (383) 7 x 9., 0965 (Box 3, Folder 228)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 6, 1886 (384) 7 x 9., 0966 (Box 3, Folder 229)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 12, 1886 (385) 5.25 x 6.75., 0967 (Box 3, Folder 230)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 6pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 13, 1886 (386) 5.25 x 6.75., 0968 (Box 3, Folder 231)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 15, 1886 (387) 5.25 x 6.75., 0975 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, December 19, 1886 (388) 5.25 x 6.75., 0978 (Box 3, Folder 233)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, December 31, 1886 (389) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 657)., 0979 (Box 3, Folder 234)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 2, 1887 (390) 6.25 x 7.75., 0982 (Box 3, Folder 235)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 4, 1887 (391) 7 x 9., 0985 (Box 3, Folder 236)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 6, 1887 (392) 7 x 9., 0989 (Box 3, Folder 237)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 8, 1887 (393) 7 x 9., 0993 (Box 3, Folder 238)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 9, 1887 (394) 7 x 9., 0998 (Box 3, Folder 239)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 13, 1887 (395) 6.25 x 7.5., 1003 (Box 3, Folder 240)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, January 23, 1887 (396) 7 x 9., 1006 (Box 3, Folder 241)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 2, 1887 (353) Cyclostyle. 8 x 4.5., 1011 (Box 3, Folder 242)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, February 3, 1887 (354) 8 x 4.5., 1016 (Box 3, Folder 243)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 4, 1887 (397) 5.25 x 6.75., 1017 (Box 3, Folder 244)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 6, 1887 (398) 5.25 x 6.75., 1022 (Box 3, Folder 245)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 13, 1887 (399) 7 x 9., 1026 (Box 3, Folder 246)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 18, 1887 (400) 7 x 9., 1030 (Box 3, Folder 247)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 18, 1887 (401) 5.25 x 6.75., 1034 (Box 3, Folder 248)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 21, 1887 (402) 5.25 x 6.75., 1038 (Box 3, Folder 249)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 22, 1887 (403) 5.25 x 6.75., 1041 (Box 3, Folder 250)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, March 6, 1887 (404) 4.5 x 7., 1044 (Box 3, Folder 251)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 7, 1887 (405) 7 x 9., 1045 (Box 3, Folder 252)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, March 8, 1887 (406) 6 x 7.5., 1048 (Box 3, Folder 253)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 13, 1887 (407) 5.25 x 7., 1049 (Box 3, Folder 254)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 17, 1887 (408) 5.25 x 7., 1053 (Box 3, Folder 255)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, march 21, 1887 (409) 5.25 x 7., 1057 (Box 3, Folder 256)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 24, 1887 (410) 5.25 x 7., 1060 (Box 3, Folder 257)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 27, 1887 (411) 6 x 7.5., 1063 (Box 3, Folder 258)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 31, 1887 (412) 7 x 9., 1070 (Box 3, Folder 259)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, April 27, 1887 (413) 7 x 9., 1074 (Box 3, Folder 260)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, June 8, 1887 (414) 7 x 9., 1078 (Box 3, Folder 261)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 14, 1887 (415) 6.25 x 7.75., 1082 (Box 3, Folder 262)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 1, 1887 (416) 5 x 8., 1083 (Box 3, Folder 263)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, October 14, 1887 (417) 6 x 7.75., 1086 (Box 3, Folder 264)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, October 16, 1887 (418) 5.25 x 6.75., 1090 (Box 3, Folder 265)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, October 31, 1887 (419) 4.5 x 7., 1094 (Box 3, Folder 266)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, November 1, 1887 (420) 4.5 x 7., 1095 (Box 3, Folder 267)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry TL, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, June 26, 1888 (421) 4.25 x 7., 1096 (Box 3, Folder 268)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, July 4, 1888 (422) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 710)., 1099 (Box 3, Folder 269)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, July 6, 1888 (423) 5 x 8., 1102 (Box 3, Folder 270)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, July 16, 1888 (424) 7 x 9., 1105 (Box 3, Folder 271)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 5pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 5, 1888 (355) Cyclostyle. 8 x 4.5 (Cohen pg. #: 712)., 1110 (Box 3, Folder 272)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 19, 1888 (425) 6 x 7.75., 1112 (Box 3, Folder 273)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 13, 1888 (356) Cyclostyle. 8 x 4.5., 1117 (Box 3, Folder 274)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, December 25, 1888 (426) 7 x 9., 1123 (Box 3, Folder 275)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 6pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 3, 1889 (427) 7 x 9., 1127 (Box 3, Folder 276)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp "Globe", January 3, 1889 (428) 5.5 x 6.75., 1134 (Box 3, Folder 277)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 6, 1889 (429) 4.5 x 7., 1138 (Box 3, Folder 278)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 8pp 190 Earl"s Court Road, January 8, 1889 (430) 7 x 9., 1141 (Box 3, Folder 279)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 11, 1889 (431) 7 x 9., 1150 (Box 3, Folder 280)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 12, 1889 (357) 4.5 x 7., 1154 (Box 3, Folder 281)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, January 15, 1889 (432) 6 x 8., 1155 (Box 3, Folder 282)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, January 20, 1889 (433) 5.5 x 6., 1160 (Box 3, Folder 283)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, January 25, 1889 (434) 7 x 9., 1165 (Box 3, Folder 284)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 6pp Christ Church, Oxford, January 29, 1889 (435) 7 x 9., 1170 (Box 3, Folder 285)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 9, 1889 (436) 6 x 7.5., 1177 (Box 3, Folder 286)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, February 12, 1889 (437) 7 x 9., 1180 (Box 3, Folder 287)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, March 15, 1889 (438) 7 x 9., 1185 (Box 3, Folder 288)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, April 12, 1889 (439) 7 x 9., 1188 (Box 3, Folder 289)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, April 17, 1889 (440) 6 x 7.75., 1192 (Box 3, Folder 290)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp Christ Church, Oxford, June 16, 1889 (441) 5.25 x 7., 1197 (Box 3, Folder 291)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 8pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, October 3, 1889 (442) 7 x 8.75., 1202 (Box 3, Folder 292)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 1p Christ Church, Oxford, November 27, 1889 (443) 4.5 x 7., 1211 (Box 3, Folder 293)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 4, 1889 (444) 4.5 x 7., 1212 (Box 3, Folder 294)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 5pp Christ Church, Oxford, December 13, 1889 (445) 6 x 7.75., 1215 (Box 3, Folder 295)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 28, 1890 (446) 5.5 x 7., 1221 (Box 3, Folder 296)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Henry ALs, 2pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, December 31, 1890 (447) 5.25 x 7., 1226 (Box 3, Folder 297)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Kitty ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 5, 1886 (363) 5.5 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 645)., 1229 (Box 3, Folder 298)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Kitty ALs,4pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 6, 1887 (364) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 687)., 1233 (Box 3, Folder 299)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Kitty ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, April 28, 1888 (365) 5.5 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 702)., 1238 (Box 3, Folder 300)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Kitty ALs, 3pp Christ Church, Oxford, Sunday Night, [April 29, 1888] (366) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 703)., 1241 (Box 3, Folder 301)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Kitty ALs, 2pp Christ Church, Oxford, November 29, 1888 (367) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 723)., 1244 (Box 3, Folder 302)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, [Kitty] ALs, 3pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 2, 1889 (369) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 726)., 1247 (Box 3, Folder 304)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Saville-Clarke, Kitty ALs, 2pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, September 29, 1889 (368) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 757)., 1251 (Box 3, Folder 303)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Scott, Clement ALs, 3pp 29 Bedford Street, Covent Garden, February 18, 1887 (XIX 510) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 664)., 1255 (Box 4, Folder 305)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Shute, Mrs. R. ALs, 4pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, December 26, 1887 (XIX 526) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 690)., 1260 (Box 4, Folder 306)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Shute, Mrs. R. ALs, 4pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, July 27, 1890 (XIX 527) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 795)., 1265 (Box 4, Folder 307)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Maud ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 12, 1886 (VII 110) Cyclostyle. 8 x 5 (Cohen pg. #: 625)., 1270 (Box 4, Folder 308)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel AL, 7pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 12, 1885 (VII 111) Signature probably excised. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 566)., 1274 (Box 4, Folder 309)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 7pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, April 4, 1885 (VII 112) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 569)., 1282 (Box 4, Folder 310)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, May 18, 1885 (VII 113) 6.25 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 575)., 1289 (Box 4, Folder 311)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 19, 1885 (VII 114) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 575)., 1290 (Box 4, Folder 312)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 20, 1885 (VII 115) 5.25 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 576)., 1293 (Box 4, Folder 313)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 22, 1885 (VII 116) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 577)., 1298 (Box 4, Folder 314)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 6pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, August 4, 1885 (VII 117) 7.75 x 4 (Cohen pg. #: 595)., 1302 (Box 4, Folder 315)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 26, 1886 (VII 118) 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 628)., 1309 (Box 4, Folder 316)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, March 30, 1886 (VII 119) 5.25 x 6.75., 1314 (Box 4, Folder 317)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 8, 1886 (VII 120) 6 x 8., 1315 (Box 4, Folder 318)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 12, 1886 (VII 121) 7 x 9., 1319 (Box 4, Folder 319)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 26, 1886 (VII 122) 6.25 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 630)., 1324 (Box 4, Folder 320)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, July 2, 1888 (VII 123) 6 x 8., 1327 (Box 4, Folder 321)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 25, 1893 (VII 124) 8 x 5.25., 1331 (Box 4, Folder 322)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Standen, Isabel ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 22, 1893 (VII 125) 7 x 9., 1334 (Box 4, Folder 323)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Enid AL, 3pp 7 Lushington Road, Eastbourne, October 23, 1893 (XII 215) Signature excised. 5.5 x 3.5 (Cohen pg. #: 990)., 1338 (Box 4, Folder 324)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. TL, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 30, 1888 (XII 194 ) With envelope. 7 x 8.75 (Cohen pg. #: 707)., 1342 (Box 4, Folder 325)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 2, 1891 (XII 195) With envelope. 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 826)., 1345 (Box 4, Folder 326)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, Mar 16, 1891 (XII 196) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 828)., 1349 (Box 4, Folder 327)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, April 1, 1891 (XII 197) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 829)., 1354 (Box 4, Folder 328)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 17, 1891 (XII 198) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 833)., 1355 (Box 4, Folder 329)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 4, 1891 (XII 199) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 838)., 1358 (Box 4, Folder 330)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, June 16, 1891 (XII 200) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 846)., 1363 (Box 4, Folder 331)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 27, 1892 (XII 201) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 904)., 1368 (Box 4, Folder 332)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 21, 1893 (XII 202) With envelope. 5.5 x 7., 1371 (Box 4, Folder 333)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 1p The Chestnuts, Guildford, June 11, 1893 (XII 203) 4.25 x 7., 1374 (Box 4, Folder 334)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, May 15, 1895 (XII 204) With envelope.. 4.25 x 7., 1375 (Box 4, Folder 335)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 3, 1896 (XII 205) 4 x 6 (Cohen pg. #: 1084)., 1376 (Box 4, Folder 336)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Mrs. N.H. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, May 22, 1896 (XII 206) With envelope. 4.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 1091)., 1379 (Box 4, Folder 337)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Winifred ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 22, 1887 (XII 208) With envelope.. 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 679)., 1380 (Box 4, Folder 338)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Winifred TL, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, June 5, 1888 (XII 209 ) With envelope. missing (Cohen pg. #: 708)., 1385 (Box 4, Folder 339)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Winifred ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 30, 1891 (XII 211) 5.5 x 3.5 (Cohen pg. #: 837)., 1386 (Box 4, Folder 340)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Winifred ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, November 20, 1891 (XII 212) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 874)., 1389 (Box 4, Folder 341)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Winifred ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, November 27, 1891 (XII 213) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 875)., 1390 (Box 4, Folder 342)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Winifred ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, December 13, 1891 (XII 214) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 876)., 1395 (Box 4, Folder 343)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Winifred ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, June 7, [n.y.] (XII 216) 5.5 x 7., undated; 1398 (Box 4, Folder 344)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stevens, Winifred] ALs, 4pp The Chestnuts, Guildford, January 1, 1895. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 1047)., 1402 (Box 4, Folder 345)
    - Dodgson Charles To Stevens Envelopes (10)., undated (Box 4, Folder 346)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Acland, Arthur] ALs, illus, 2pp [Christ, Church, Oxford], February 7, 1881 (XI 153 ) 6 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 407)., 1407 (Box 4, Folder 347)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Acland, Arthur] ALs, 3pp [Christ, Church, Oxford], November 19, 1886 (XI 154) 6 x 7.75 (Cohen pg. #: 650)., 1410 (Box 4, Folder 348)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 4pp Christ, Church, Oxford, December 11, 1886 (XI 155) 5.5 x 6.75 (Cohen pg. #: 655)., 1414 (Box 4, Folder 349)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 13, 1888 (XI 156) 7 x 9., 1418 (Box 4, Folder 350)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 16, 1888 (XI 157) 7 x 4.5., 1421 (Box 4, Folder 351)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 1p [Christ, Church, Oxford], February 18, 1888 (XI 158) 4 x 6., 1424 (Box 4, Folder 352)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 19, 1888 (XI 159) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 701)., 1425 (Box 4, Folder 353)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 24, 1888 (XI 160) 5 x 8., 1429 (Box 4, Folder 354)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, December 24, [1889] (XI 162) 4 x 6.25 (Cohen pg. #: 771)., 1446 (Box 4, Folder 355)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 3pp [Christ, Church, Oxford], February 24, [1890], 4:35 p.m. (XI 161) 5.5 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 778)., 1442 (Box 4, Folder 356)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, November 12, 1890 (XI 163) 4.5 x 7., 1432 (Box 4, Folder 357)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 13, 1891 (XI 164) 5 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 831)., 1433 (Box 4, Folder 358)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, June 30, 1891 (XI 165) 5 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 848)., 1436 (Box 4, Folder 359)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Steward, Christ Church [Sadler, Michael] ALs, illus, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 2, 1893 (XI 166) 5 x 8 (Cohen pg. #: 944)., 1439 (Box 4, Folder 360)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, Professor J.A. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, June 8, 1881 (X 132) With envelope. 7 x 9 (Cohen pg. #: 432)., 1449 (Box 4, Folder 361)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, February 10, 1886 (X 133) 4.5 x 7., 1450 (Box 4, Folder 362)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, April 12, 1889 (X 134) 7 x 4.5 (Cohen pg. #: 738)., 1453 (Box 4, Folder 363)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, November 11, 1892 (X 136) 5.5 x 7., 1456 (Box 4, Folder 364)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, March 25, 1893 (X 138)See manuscripts. Possibly refers to manuscript to Stewart dated March 23, 1893. 3.75 x 6. (Box 4, Folder 365)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, February 10, 1894 (X 139) With envelope. 8.5 x 8.5., 1458 (Box 4, Folder 366)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, March 8, 1894 (X 140) With envelope. 3.5 x 5.25., 1459 (Box 4, Folder 367)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1pp Christ, Church, Oxford, March 12, 1894 (X 141) With AN, 1p dated "12/3/94.". 5.75 x 8.75., 1460 (Box 4, Folder 368)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. Als, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, March 22, 1894 (X 142) 4.5 x 7., 1463 (Box 4, Folder 369)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. Als, 1p Christ, Church, Oxford, December 14, 1897 (X 143) With envelope. 4.25 x 7., 1464 (Box 4, Folder 370)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Stewart, J.A. ALs, 1p [n.p., n.d.] (X 135) With envelope. 4 x 6.25., undated; 1465 (Box 4, Folder 371)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Ellen Als, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, June 12, 1897. 7 x 9., 1466 (Box 4, Folder 372)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Florence Als, 2pp Christ, Church, Oxford, December 22, [1881] (574) 5.25 x 7 (Cohen pg. #: 449)., 1469 (Box 4, Folder 373)
    - Dodgson, Charles To Terry, Lewis Als, 3pp Christ, Church, Oxford, May 8, 1879 (573) 7 x 9., 1472 (Box 4, Folder 374)